Guide to the Wanda Gifford Photographs 1948-1958
Oregon State University Libraries, University Archives
- Numbered Photographs, 1948-1957; Series I; 1946 negatives and 884 prints
  - A stuck truck, 0493b; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Santiam Highway near Sisters, Oregon through sugar pines, 0494; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Blue Lake high in the Cascade Range; lake can be seen from the Santiam highway, 0495; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Virginia Gritton inside of tile pipe, 0496; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Plowing at Soil Conservation Demonstration, 0497; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Ford tractor demonstrating a circular cultivator, 0498; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Caterpillar tractor and scraper; B? demonstration digging pond, 0500; 3 prints and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    3 views
  - Bucyrus Erie backhoe at work, 0501; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Bucyrus Erie backhoe digging ditch; front view, 0502; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - International tractor demonstration sub soiler (Soil Conservation Demonstration), 0503; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Lunch line up (Soil Conservation Demonstration), 0504; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Field of cars at Soil Conservation Demonstration, 0505; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Loran 75-D backhoe at work on City of Salem Server project, 0506-509; 3 prints and 4 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Open sewer trench and tile in ditch, 0510; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Little girl with bugle, hat and Oregon State t-shirt, 0512; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Jim Schwab ties a load of steaming mint refuse to be hauled to dump to rot; Henry Turnridge farm near Jefferson, Oregon, 0515; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Ben Newell home (1/25 at F16; cloudy, hazy day), 0516; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Hillar Ibach plowing on new John Deere tractor, Tualatin, Oregon, 0517; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - First day of school, Highland School, 1949; 0519
    - 5 120 negatives (Box 10)
    - 3 prints and 1 oversize print (Box 5, 76)
  - Black Angus herd, eastern Oregon below Burns, 0520; 2 prints and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Driving herefords along road below Burns, Oregon, 0521; 2 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - John Deer tractor at work at State Fair, 0522; print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Night shot State Fair, 0523; 120 negative (Box 10)
  - Miscellaneous pictures of cabin porch, river, and lake, 0524; 8 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - Steens Mountain area?, 0525; 38 120 negatives
    - Farm backyard, 120 negative; 0525.1 (Box 10)
    - Farm house, 120 negative; 0525.2 (Box 10)
    - Long shot of fence, fields, and hills, print and 120 negative; 0525.3 (Box 5, 10)
    - Deer hunters bathing feet in creek, 120 negatives; 0525.4-5 (Box 10)
    - Trucks at gate to fields; farm in background, 120 negatives; 0525.6-7 (Box 10)
    - Barn, 120 negative; 0525.8 (Box 10)
    - Overview of farms and field, 120 negative; 0525.9 (Box 10)
    - Small home and hills, 120 negative; 0525.10 (Box 10)
    - Small stream, 120 negative; 0525.11 (Box 10)
    - Stream in meadow Steens?, 120 negatives; 0525.12-525.14 (Box 10)
    - Hills, 120 negatives; 0525.15 (Box 10)
    - Horses, 120 negatives; 0525.16-525.17 (Box 10)
    - Road; farm in distant background, 120 negative; 0525.18 (Box 10)
    - Farm and fields, 120 negative; 0525.19 (Box 10)
    - Woman overlooking valley, 120 negatives; 0525.20-525.21 (Box 10)
    - Valley of fields, 120 negative; 0525.22 (Box 10)
    - Horses, 120 negative; 0525.23 (Box 10)
    - Stream, 120 negative; 0525.24 (Box 10)
    - Small log cabin, 120 negative; 0525.25 (Box 10)
    - Cabin, 120 negative; 0525.26 (Box 10)
    - Something hanging to dry, 120 negative; 0525.27 (Box 10)
    - Road with valley in background, 120 negative; 0525.28 (Box 10)
    - Road through field, 120 negative; 0525.29 (Box 10)
    - Horses in pasture, 120 negative; 0525.30 (Box 10)
    - Horses, 120 negative; 0525.31-525.34 (Box 10)
    - Overview of valley, 120 negatives; 0525.35 (Box 10)
    - Horses, 120 negative; 0525.36 (Box 10)
    - Horses on pasture, 120 negative; 0525.37 (Box 10)
    - Saddled horses, 120 negative; 0525.38 (Box 10)
  - Playground equipment at Highland school, 0526; print and 3 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Girl leading cow into ring at State Fair, 0527; 3 120 negatives (Box 10)
    Girl leading cow into ring (527a); Girl showing her Jersey dairy cow (527b); Showing Jersey cows at Oregon State Fair (527c)
  - Sewer construction, 0528; 120 negative (Box 10)
  - Baby Hagedorn, 4x5 negative; 0529 (Box 10)
  - Circular chicken house, Lee Hatchery, 2 4x5 negatives; 0531 (Box 10)
  - Pen of chickens at circular laying house, Lee Hatchery; white leghorns, 2 4x5 negatives; 0532 (Box 10)
  - Hancock Family; groups and individuals, 10 4x5 negatives; 0533 (Box 10)
  - Hagedorn baby, Christmas time, 1949; 3 4x5 negatives; 0535 (Box 10)
  - Frank Dommly farm near Newburg; new silo, herefords, new pig house, etc., 1949; 0536; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Paper mill on the Willamette River at Oregon City, Oregon, 0537
    early morning light; 1/100 at F11; K2 filter
    - 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 2 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Grade A Dairy Barn on road between Woodburn and Newberg, 0538; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Willamette Falls, Oregon City, 2 prints and 4x5 negative; 0539 (Box 5, 10)
  - Jerry Winsor (Vernon's boy) sky, print and 2 4x5 negatives; 0540 (Box 5, 10)
  - Winsor family, 2 4x5 negatives; 0541 (Box 10)
  - Winsor daughter, 5 4x5 negatives; 0542 (Box 10)
  - Interior of James Dougherty's new barn, Woodburn, Oregon, 4x5 negative; 0543 (Box 10)
  - James Dougherty and cattle in his new dairy barn near Woodburn, 0544; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Exterior of James Dougherty's barn, 0545; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    2 views; 1/25 at F11; cloudy day
  - Newton Davis loafing shed, Woodburn, Oregon; near Broadacres, 0546-547; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Pigs beside road, 0548; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Hereford pigs; bought from Schmidt of Newburg, 0549; prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Dairy Barn by road in snow, Mosley place, 0552; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Damage to 12th St., Salem, Oregon, freeze, 1950; 0553; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Cutting alta fescue, Harry Riches farm, Waldo Hills, 1949; 0554; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Salem Sewer project, showing long rows of conduit at Shipping St. intersection, 0555; 7 prints and 4 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Livestock Association Christmas party, Silverton Grange Hall, 1949; 0556; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Detroit Dam construction, 0557; 9 prints and 22 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    Highway 22; Highway 22 (557c); Detroit, Oregon (557e); Detroit Dam construction site (557f); Detroit Dam construction site (557i); Detroit Dam construction site (557j); Highway 22 (557t)
  - Breitenbush Bridge, 4x5 negative; 0558 (Box 10)
  - Old road near ranger station, Detroit, Oregon, 4x5 negative; 0559 (Box 10)
  - North Santiam Rd., 0560; print and 6 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Dam area looking east, Detroit, Oregon, 4x5 negative; 0561 (Box 10)
  - North Santiam Rd., 4x5 negative; 0562 (Box 10)
  - Lidbeck home snow, 0563; 2 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - Willamette University campus in snow, winter 1950 snow, 0564; 3 prints and 3 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Country road surrounded with snow, 0565; 1 print and 4 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - "Oregon Snow Scape"; Pringle Creek snow, 1950; 0566; print and 3 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    Camera Rollicord; K2 filter; Super XX film; Developed in Microdol; Print Kodabromide F3; Exposure 1/100 at F11
  - House next to Iufers, snow, 1950; 0567; print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - "Winter Morn" Ernest Iufer's home, near Salem, Oregon, 1950 snow, 0568; print of view a and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    camera Rollicord; film Super XX; Time about 8 am; K2 filter; 1/100 at F11
  - Snow covered tree and house on the Stayton highway, Silverton, Oregon, 1950; 0569; print and 120 negative (Box 5, 10)
    See also image 0583.
  - Bush home on Mission; snow, 1950; 0570; 2 prints and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Oregon State Capitol shots; snow, 1950; 0571; 3 prints and 6 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Snow scenes, 0572; 1 print and 19 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Anthol? Rhiney, 2 pig club boar, Jeldwich's? boy, 0573; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Road covered in snow, 0574; print and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Winter farm scene, Stayton, Oregon, 0575
    - 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
    - 2 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Snow covered country road and billboard, 0576; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Orchard covered with snow, 0577
    - 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
    - 3 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Car on snow covered country road, 0578; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Flax Bean shot; near 4 corners; snow, 0579; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Farm covered in snow, 0580; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Snow shot; road, 0581
    - 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 2 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Car driving down snowy road, 0582; prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - House on hill; tree; snow scene, 0583
    Similar to image 0569.
    - 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 2 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Car on road next to snow covered farm, 0584; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Big barn, Wolfe place?, 0585; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Althea and snow trees, 0586; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Loading South Pacific rail car, 0587; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Just barley, 0588; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
    Close-up.
  - North Santiam Highway, Oregon, Santiam River and the tip of Mt. Jefferson showing in the background, 0589; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Small canyon, 4x5 negative; 0590 (Box 10)
  - Detroit Dam, 0591; 13 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - Registered short hair sire owned by Chris Jorgenson, Jefferson, Oregon, 0593; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Short horn bull, 5 years old, owned by Chirs Jorgenson, Jefferson, Oregon, 4x5 negative; 0594 (Box 10)
  - Shorthorn sire, Santiam Master, owned by Mr. Chris Jorgenson, Jefferson, Oregon, 0595; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Three of the young shorthorn calves owned by Chris Jorgenson of Jefferson, Oregon, 0596; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Cows in barnyard, 0597; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Boy helping calf stand, 0598; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - State office building, 0599; 1 print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Base of tree with crocuses blooming; boy at base of tree, 0600; print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - 1950 snow shots, 0601; 3 120 negatives (Box 10)
  - U.S. Post Office building, Salem, 0602; print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Small bridge over flowing ditch, 0603; 120 negative (Box 10)
  - Drainage of lowlands near 99E south of Salem, 0604; 3 prints and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Marion County Courthouse, 0605; print and 2 120 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - George Arbuckle's Palameno colt; 1 week old, March 12, 1950; 0606; 3 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Betty Jean Voght with Graymere Dear Lollie, a 6 years old Jersey cow (best view), 0607-0608; 2 prints and 2 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Betty Jean Voght with Graymere Dear Lollie's 5th calf; calf is 3 months old, 0609; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Close up of Betty Jean Voght and Graymere Dear Lollie, 1950; 0610; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Betty Jean Voght and her registered Jersey Graymere Dear Lollie; front view, 0611; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Betty Jean Voght and the 3 month old calf of Graymere Dear Lollie, 1950; 0612; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Henry Torn registered calves in front of his home, Champoeg, Oregon, March 12, 1950; 0613-614; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Henry Torn home, Champoeg, Oregon; calves in foreground, March 12, 1950; 0615; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Interior of milk house; sink, cans, etc., 0616; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Henry Torn milking parlor, 0617; print and 3 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Berry field, spring of 1950; 0619; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Disking berry field; Paul Townsend near Wheatland, 0620; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Disking berry field, 0621; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Spraying cherries, 0622; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Spraying cherries, 0623; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Apple orchard in full bloom, 0624; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Bud Anderson disking cover crop in peach orchard, 0625-0627; prints for 626 & 627 and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    - 0625, 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 0626, print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
    - 0627, print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Men hanging strings for growing hops, 0628-629; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Carol Cantway at shower, 0630; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Paul Townsend herefords, 0631; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Cows in pasture, 0632; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Crowd gathered around speaker, 0633; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Men walking up car-lined road, 0634; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pasture tour, 0635; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pasture tour of Swanson farm, 0636; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Cows in pasture, H.A. Barnes, 0637; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Mr. H.A. Barnes and Albert Julian, of Lyons, inspect fine stand of subterranian clover and fescue, 0638; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Three wooly lambs, 0639; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Wooly lambs, 0640; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Man standing on stump, 0641; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Chet Mulkey Band, 0642; 2 prints and 5 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Pigs in barnyard, 0643; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Colt with mother, 0644; print and 3 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Man on tractor in vineyard, 0645; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Registered Duroc pig owned by Mr. George Krause, Silverton, Oregon, 0646; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Man holding piglet with mother and piglets at his feet, 0647; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mother and her piglets, 0648; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Sign for Registered Durocs (bred gilts & herd sires), Geo. F. Kraus & Sons, 0649; print and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Interior shots of Mr. and Mrs. Geo Kraus, 0650; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Man with pig, 0651; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Man putting piglet in pen, 0652; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Long shot of a farm, 0653; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Pigs, 0654; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pig, 0656; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pigs, 0657; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Pioneer and his open gilts all sired by him, 0658; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pruned branches beneath trees in an orchard, 0659; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Orchard trees framed between oaks, 0660; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Orchard, 0661; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    Good shot well framed road; similar to image 0691.
  - Orchard framed between oaks, 0662; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
    Similar to image 0660.
  - Orchard and overhanging cherry limb (good clouds), 0663; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Blooming orchard, 0664-0666
    - 0664, 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 0665-0666, 2 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Blooming orchard; hills in background, 0667; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Blooming orchard (good shot), 0668; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Vertical shot of a blooming orchard, 0669; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Vertical shot of a blooming orchard, 0670; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Barn with silo, 0671; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Spraying carola thistle in grain field with tractor, 0672; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Clem Bering Holstein herd at milking time, 1950; 0673; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Cows in field, 0674; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Cows in field, 0675; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - World record Holstein cow owned by Clem Bering, Mt. Angel, 0676; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - World record Holstein cow, Nuggett, owned by Clem Bering, Mt. Angel, Oregon, 0677; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Pigs in barnyard, 0678; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Registered Guernsey herd on the G. Brandt farm, Silverton, Oregon, 0679-0680; 4 prints and 2 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Cows in field, 0681; 4 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Registered Guernsey yearling calves owned by George Brandt of Silverton, Oregon, 0682; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Registered Guernsey calves owned by G. Brandt, Silverton, Oregon, 0683; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Covered bridge at Scotts Mills, Oregon, 0684; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Covered bridge at Scotts Mills Oregon; log truck entering, 0685; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Interior of covered bridge looking toward sawmill; evening, 0686; 3 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Abiqua river at Scott Mills, Oregon, 0687; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Edward Nefsiger farm shop; welding, 0688-689; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Carl Vogt farm shop, 0690; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Man working in shop, 0691; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Man working in shop, 0692; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Man working in shop repairing lawn mower, 0693; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Storage shed for farm equipment, 0694; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Looking into small storage shed, 0695; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Storage shed, 0696; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Archie McCorkle examines his heavy clover cover crop under pear trees late one evening, 0697-698; 3 prints and 2 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Farmall Super A, Stanley Sneed, in strawberry field, 0699-700; print for 699 and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    - 0699, print and 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
    - 0700, 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Young man in a strawberry field near Salem, Oregon, 0701-702
    - 0701, 4x5 negative (Box 10)
    - 702, print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Man with cow, 0703; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Cows lined up in a row, 0704-0705; 4x5 diacetate negatives (Box 67)
  - Mr. Vick Forester, Sherwood, Oregon with string of Jersey cows, 0706; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Man with bull, 0707; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Jersey sire, Glow, owned by Newton Davis, Woodburn, Oregon, 0708; 2 prints and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Mr. Vick Forester, with Jersey cow, Sherwood, Oregon, 0709; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Milking time, Davis farm, 0710; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Registered Jersey herd at the Newt Davis farm, Woodburn, Oregon, 0711; 4 prints and 6 4x5 negatives (Box 5, 10)
  - Onion field near Brooks, 0712; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Automobile accident, 0713-0714; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Girl standing by a table, 0715; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - 2 girls sitting on a couch, 0716; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - 2 men on a tractor, 0717; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Roy Rutchsman working in his farm shop, Silverton, Oregon, 0718; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Tractor pulling hay wagon, 0719-720; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Jim Dougherty cows, 0721; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Cows in a field, 0722; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Cows in a field, 0723; 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 67)
  - Grape vines waiting to be harvested, 0724; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Frank A. Johnson admires a bunch of his well-grown grapes (Concord variety), Salem, Oregon, 0725; 2 prints and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Frank A. Johnson weighing his grapes, 0726; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Frank A. Johnson picking grapes, 0727; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Grapes on the vine, 0728-0729
    - 2 120 negatives (Box 10)
    - 3 prints (Box 5, 76)
  - Ready to pick Spitzenburg apples, 0730; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Ready to pick apples, 0731-0733
    - 0731, 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
    - 0732-0733, 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - Ready to pick Spitzenburg apples, 0734; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Mt. Rundle; Bauer? Lake, 0735; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Lake Louise, Canada, 0736; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Moraine Lake Valley of Ten Peaks, Canada, 0737; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Lake Louise; hotel across lake, 0738; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mt. Temple near camp, 0739; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Mt. Temple at camp, Canada, 0740; 4x5 negative (Box 10)
  - Bow River and Valley as seen from veranda of hotel at Banff, Canada, 0741; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Banff, Canada from administration building; flowers in foreground; street and mountains, 0742; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Bow Lake, Canada; boats in foreground, 0743; 4 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - At road to Sun Mountain Glacier National Park; Eva and Francis at stone wall, 0744; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - View of a river canyon, 0745; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - On road to "Medicine Lake," Glacier National Park; Eva in foreground, 0746; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - On the road to Medicine Lake, Glacier National Park, 0747; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Glacial waters, Columbia ice fields, 0748; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 10)
  - Valley of Ten Peaks from Moraine Lake, 0749-0750; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 10)
  - View of mountains, lake and river, 0751; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Peyto Glacier, 0752; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Glacier and delpheniams [sic] at Lake Louise, Canada, 0753; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - On road to ski lift Banff; Eva near tree with mountain in background, 0754; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Bow Lake; stream in foreground, 0755; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - View of a mountain lake, 0756; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - View of a mountain lake, 0757; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Valley of Ten Peaks, 0758; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mountains reflected in a lake (Ten Peaks?), 0759; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Temple Pipestone River at Lake Louise, 0760; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Valley of Ten Peaks from Moraine Lake (vertical shot), 0761; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Family in front of hotel depicted in image 0738, 0762; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Boat dock on lake; mountain in background, 0763; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Athabaska Glacier; Columbia Ice Fields, 0764; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Temple from camp, 0765; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Columbia ice fields, 0766-0767; 2 4x5 negatives (Box 11)
  - Reflection in Hubert Lake, 0768; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Large lake with mountain in background, 0769; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mountains reflecting in a lake, 0770; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mountains reflecting in a lake, 0771; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mountains reflecting in a lake, 0772; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Canadian Rockies and railway, Canada, 0773; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mt. Eisenhouer, 0774; print and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - Mountains reflecting in a lake, 0775; 2 prints and 4x5 negative (Box 5, 11)
  - The Great Divide between British Columbia and Alberta, Alberta side, 0776; print and 4x5 diacetate negative (Box 5, 67)
  - Vertical shot of a steep mountain canyon, 0777; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Kicking Horse Canyon, 0778; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - A melting glacier with a mountain in the background, 0779; 2 4x5 diacetate negatives (Box 67)
  - Mountain range, 0780; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - A resort with a mountain backdrop, 0781; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - Mt. Eisenhour, Canada, 0782; 4x5 negative (Box 11)
  - A mountain lake, 0783; 4x5 negative (Box 11)